maemo.org 2010-06-26

# maemo.org - Privacy Policy: Privacy Policy of maemo.org

(Version 1/2005, posted and effective as of 25th May 2005) 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to the www.maemo.org web site and the services provided therein (the “Site”), operated by Nokia Corporation, its subsidiaries or affiliates (“Nokia”) from which you have accessed this Privacy Policy. By accessing and using the Site, you expressly agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Site and not necessarily to other sites of Nokia. This Site may contain links to other sites. Nokia does not share your personal information with those sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. When leaving this Site, please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are thereafter visiting. 

**If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. By accessing and using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.**

**Visitor Identification (“Cookies”) and Non-Personal Information**

Nokia or its third-party designees may place information on your computer to allow Nokia to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as "cookies". The cookies used by Nokia or its third-party designees on the Site are session-specific and are cancelled and expire when you leave the Site and are not stored on your computer. The data collected through cookies does not, in any way, identify you personally or your computer. The information collected is collected for technical and maintenance purposes only. 

Please note that Nokia may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifiable information. 

**Personal Information Collected**

Nokia is committed to the protection of the privacy of its Site visitors. Nokia stores personal informa-tion that you may provide to Nokia, or that Nokia may receive in connection with the Site and the services provided on this Site. Such information may include, among other information, your name, e-mail address and information about your responses to the Site, campaigns and other activities, as well as about your contacts with the support personnel of the Site ("Personal Information"). In the event you are of the age of a minor or otherwise a minor in your country, you may need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to Nokia via the Site. 

**Purposes for which Personal Information is Collected**

Nokia collects Personal Information for the purposes of provision, development and personalization of the Site and any other Nokia sites, services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics and customer care. Specifically, Nokia collects Personal Information for the purposes of personal communication with you in order to respond to your questions, and fulfill your requests. And, in the event you have so consented, to contact you for direct marketing purposes via e-mail and to inform you of and get your feedback on upcoming products, services and/or promotions of Nokia or third parties. 

**Information Storage and Processing**

The Personal Information relating to the Site will be stored, processed and used in accordance with applicable data protection regulations by Nokia Corporation, P.O. Box 100, FIN-00045 Nokia Group, Finland. The Personal Information is stored by Nokia either on servers in Finland or in some other country within the European Union. Nokia may consolidate the consumer databases. 

You expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that your Personal Information gained in connection with your use of the Site, with respect to the Site, may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site (mirror sites), including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration, for operating and developing the Site or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant database, which may be located in Finland or in some other country or countries within the European Union. 

You expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that Nokia, Nokia’s subcontractors or agents performing support and thereto related tasks may have access to your Personal Information in order to complete the task in question. These entities performing these functions have accepted appropriate confidentiality obligations when processing your personal information. Your Personal Information will not be revealed to any third parties without your prior consent, except as otherwise provided above in this Privacy Policy or required by law, court order or law enforcement officials. 

**Security, Review and Accuracy of Personal Information**

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or any other media or terminal, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker-proof", Nokia has endeavored to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your Per-sonal Information. 

You have the right at any time to review any and all of your Personal Information stored by Nokia. Further, you have the right, at any time, to ask Nokia to remove some or all of your Personal Information and to prohibit Nokia or its third-party designees from using any Personal Information submitted by or collected from you. 

Nokia will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated Personal Information retained by Nokia in connection with the operation of the Site. To exercise these rights with respect to your Personal Information please contact webhost@maemo.org 

**Modification of the Privacy Policy**

Nokia reserves the right to change or modify at any time without prior notice this Privacy Policy. Nokia will notify you of such change or modification by posting an updated version of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy. Continued use of the Site shall constitute your consent to such changes.
